<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project on Linlin Li&#39;s Data Science Project Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/categories/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project on Linlin Li&#39;s Data Science Project Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 22:40:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://linlin-li-1.github.io/categories/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Two-stage CNN-based 3D Object Classification</title>
      <link>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/11/two-stage-cnn-based-3d-object-classification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 22:40:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/11/two-stage-cnn-based-3d-object-classification/</guid>
      <description>In this post I’ll be discussing my final project for ECE 685: Deep Learning, a course I took at Duke University. For this project, Jiawei Chen and I proposed a two-stage algorithm to improve classification accuracy. You can find my Github repository for this blog here.
Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) have been used on 3D point clouds for object classification. However, due to the nature of the CNNs, classifiers, especially those CNN-based classifiers, are usually confused about objects that look alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Analysis</title>
      <link>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/11/covid-19-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 17:20:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/11/covid-19-analysis/</guid>
      <description>1. Background COVID-19, a disease caused by a new type of coronavirus, has become a major global human threat that has turned into a pandemic. During this period, the role of the immune system has attracted people&#39;s attention. Some researchers identified some important nutritional considerations for the prevention and management of COVID-19 diseases (Yasemin Ipek Ayseli et al., 2020). Based on these studies, some &amp;quot;experts&amp;quot; and articles have urged people to buy supplements or eat particular foods to enhance their immune system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>