<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Linlin Li&#39;s Data Science Project Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Linlin Li&#39;s Data Science Project Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 12:08:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://linlin-li-1.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How terrible is the occurrence of malaria?</title>
      <link>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/09/how-terrible-is-the-occurrence-of-malaria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 12:08:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/09/how-terrible-is-the-occurrence-of-malaria/</guid>
      <description>Malaria is a serious and sometimes fatal disease caused by a parasite that commonly infects a certain type of mosquito which feeds on humans. People who get malaria are typically very sick with high fevers, shaking chills, and flu-like illness. Because malaria causes so much illness and death, the disease is a great drain on many national economies. Since many countries with malaria are already among the poorer nations, the disease maintains a vicious cycle of disease and poverty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 problems on Euler Project</title>
      <link>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/08/3-problems-on-euler-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 12:23:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/08/3-problems-on-euler-project/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I would share my solutions to 3 problems of Project Euler using Python. The problems on Project Euler are designed according to the &amp;quot;one-minute rule&amp;quot;, which shows that an efficient implementation will allow a solution to be obtained in less then one minute. This is a good website where you can practice designing efficient algorithms for many difficult problems. I will continue to resolve problems on this website and update this blog in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a personal website on Github Pages using Hugo</title>
      <link>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/08/how-to-build-a-personal-website-on-github-pages-using-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 13:14:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/08/how-to-build-a-personal-website-on-github-pages-using-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In this article, I would share my experiences and the steps I took when building a personal website on GitHub Pages using Hugo. To build a personal website, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to have knowledge other than writing Markdown. It&amp;rsquo;s simple, let&amp;rsquo;s go!
You can find my Github repository for this blog here.
Step 1: Install Git Git is a free and open source distributed version control system designed to handle everything from small to very large projects with speed and efficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/08/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 01:33:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://linlin-li-1.github.io/2020/08/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Nice to meet you, and welcome to Linlin Li&amp;rsquo;s website! I am Linlin Li, a student in the Master’s of Statistical Science program at Duke University.
I have always been eager to create a personal website to write interesting things and record my own growth. Fortunately, one of my courses requires me to update on my website, and I took this opportunity to make this idea come true. In the beginning, I planned to focus on documenting data science projects for future reference and let the website record the track of my learning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>